You all have everything, right?
You've got lunch, water bottles, and your snacks?
Yes!
Fujimoto, Kobato, you've both got everything, right?
Yeah.
Aren't you bringing anything?
Woops, sorry, lemme go get my bag!
Are you okay, Kobato?
I'm fine.
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
... Little hide-and-seek.
What're you doing, Kobato?
Let's go, Ioryogi!
We're all going on a field trip!
I knew you were excited about something.
Yeah!  It's gonna be so much fun!
You should come too!
I guess.
Ummmm...
What are you doing?  You're the only one here!
Yeah!
Hanato Kobato speaking!
Kobato?
Oh, whoops, this is the Yomogi Nursery!
Who're you?
I work here!
You sound perky.
Thanks.
Can you put me on to Sayaka?
Um...  She's out on a field trip.
What can I do for you?
How about this.
Take a message for her.
Okay!
She needs to fold up shop and get out of there.
I'm not giving her any longer.
Are you a loan shark?
You're one of the ones who came by and was mean to everyone!
They were?
Sorry!
Why are you apologizing?
For getting angry at you for something you didn't do.
You're a funny one.
What's up?
Anyway, too bad, but looks like you're out of work.
I'm shutting down the nursery.
No way...
All right, go tell Sayaka.
Who are you!?
Shutting down the nursery?
I wonder if he's an acquaintance of Miss Sayaka.
I'll pass on the trip.
Ioryogi!?
I think I'm just gonna take a nap instead.
What's taking her so long?
How long do you expect us to wait?
We're gonna be late.
Does Miss Sayaka know a loan shark?
Huh?
A man called just now...
He said he was shutting down the nursery.
Him?
Don't tell Miss Sayaka about the call.
But he sounded so scary...
Just shut up about it.
Kobato, Fujimoto, let's get going!
Sorry, we'll be right there.
You always put the entrance somewhere weird, don't you.
Hey!
Yo.
Oh, it's just you.
Isn't the name a bit overkill?
I didn't have any choice in the matter.  They picked it out fo me, same as the work itself.
That guy went ahead and got that involved?
Don't call him "that guy".
That body not enough of a lesson for you?
What do you mean, lesson?  It wasn't my fault!
After the mess you made--!
You're still on about that!?
If he heard you say that, you'd end up something worse than a stuffed animal.
Maybe a finger pupper or something.
But enough about that.
What are you here for today?
It's not just to act important, I hope.
There's something I want you to check out.
Sit down and let me hear it.
Wow, it's so high!
Hey, look over there!
At what?
Hey, look, a big pond!
Shutting down the nursery.
I wonder who made that call this morning.
Kobato!  Toshihiko!  Marina!
It's lunchtime!
Okay!
It's swelling...
You keep hurting yourself today.
You seem so distracted.
Are you worried about something, Kobato?
Umm...
Nah, she's always an airhead.
I'm not always an airhead!
Don't get Miss Sayaka all worried, okay?
Okay...
So you wanna hear about Yomogi Nursery and the people who work there?
Yeah.
What, gotten rusty at your old information-gathering tricks in that pitiful little body of yours?
Yours is a million times worse.
But I didn't expect you to put it like that.
You used to just tell me to check things out, no questions asked.
If I didn't listen, you'd spit fire or smack me.
Fine, if you want it that way here's a nice big one.
Knock it off!
Hold on, they're burning.
You're way too used to this job.
Man, your old lackeys would cry if they saw you now.
I don't wanna hear that from a stuffed animal.
What'd you just say!?
I'll check out what you asked about.
It's got something to do with that girl, right?
Yeah.  Thanks.
If you want it so bad.
Yum-yum.
Hey, paws off!
Kobato!
Marina!
What's up?
Are you worried about something?
Well, umm...
No!  Nothing at all!
... Yeah, you are.
It's okay.  I know something.
If we find it, it'll make you happy!
Kobato!  Over here!
Let's play hide and seek!
Okay!
I'll be right there!
Rock-paper-scissors! Rock-paper-scissors!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Kobato, you're it!
All right, let's all hide while Kobato counts to ten!
You'd better come find us!
All right!  I'll try my best!
This all you're giving me to take back?
C'mon...
I can take a few dozen more!
Man, this body sucks.
And it's pitiful too.
I don't wanna hear that from you.
It's been a while, Ginsei.
It really is shameful.
So what?
Same book, different cover, huh.
Aren't you coming back to the other world?
I've got something I have to do.
That girl?
Touch Kobato and I'll kill you.
Don't forget.
We'll settle things someday.
Man, he's annoying.
Where did you all hide?
Not here...
Where did you all go!?
Wow, Kobato looks like she's having a lot of fun.
She hasn't even found one of us.
She keeps looking in weird places.
This is probably gonna take a while.
You're all so good at hiding!
Hey!
Fujimoto!
It's about time to go home.
No way!  I'm it!
Huh?
It has to find everyone who's hiding!
I guess, but it's getting pretty late.
Time to go home, everyone!
There they are!
Kobato, are you okay?
I found Toshihiko and Yoshio!
Yeah, you found us!
I found Izuru and Yukari!
I found Masao!  And there's someone over there!
And over there!
You've still got a leaf stuck in your hair!
You're so clumsy.  I'll get it out for you.
Thanks!
All right, let's go.
Okay!
Let's take a picture to remember by before that, though.
Huh?  Where's Marina?
She's gone.
I'll go look for her.
Fujimoto...
Sayaka, you stay here with everyone.
I'll go look too!
Marina!
Did you find her?
No!
Maybe she's still hiding somewhere.
I sure hope so.
If I had found her sooner...
Let's look over there.
Marina!
Marina!?
She's sleeping...
I'm glad we found her.
Marina!
Good morning!
Kobato?
Sorry I couldn't find one.
You mean in hide and seek?
No, four-leaf clovers.
If you find one, you'll be happy.
I wanted to give you one.
Me?
You seemed so sad today.
I looked all over, but there weren't any...
Sorry.
It's okay if you didn't find any.
I'm happy now.
I'm happy just because you tried to make me happy.
That's nice!
This is a nice view.  We should take a picture.
All right, stand still!
Hurry up, Mr. Kiyokazu!
I'm fine.  Just face the camera.
What's she--
I found one!
A four-leaf clover!
Here!
Thanks, Kobato!
Look, Kobato!
Look!
There's tons of them!
So we've found a lot of happiness, right?
Hey!
I'm taking another picture!
Okay!
Man, your baumkuchen are a mess.
And to think that you just got them from Genko.
Man, one thing after another.
You're one of that bear's lackeys?
The name's, uh...
Welp, I forgot.
Come on!  I'm Zuisho!
I have a message for Genko!
He finished your investigation.
What!?
I knew he could do it.
Dunno how you got him to do it like that.
You birdbrain!
I'm home!
Huh?
Ioryogi's not back yet.
Oh no!  He's small, so maybe he got caught between something,
or fell in a hole,
or got sat on!
Oh no, Ioryogi's in trouble!
Who's in trouble?
Ioryogi!
Welcome home!
What's that?
This?
It's baumkuchen.
So, how'd the field trip go?
I brought you a souvenir!
Here!
It's a clover of happiness!
Happiness has found you, even though it's a little bit wilted now.
I hope everyone from the Yomogi Nursery can stay happy forever.
Here's the report.  The previous headmaster of Yomogi Nursery got conned into borrowing a lot of money.
The previous headmaster?
Yes.  Okiura Sayaka's father.  He died two years ago.
The guys who did it are a pretty tough bunch, but one of them has some connections with Sayaka.
Sounds like trouble.
If this keeps up, sooner or later Yomogi Nursery will be shut down.
People all want to fly
but they're cheated by gravity
everyone can really fly
She must be so unhappy because
she forgot her own shadow somewhere
Then...
If you tell me "thanks", if you say "thanks" and smile
Going back and forth, we'll be happy
You'll be happy, there'll be nothing to worry about
As long as we're together
It's strange, I'm crying even though I'm happy
... A kind person.
Next episode